Bienen, Leigh B.; Papers apap312
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material, 1979-2011, Undated; 2; 7 cubic ft.
  - Mary E. Forsberg, "Money for Nothing? The Financial Cost of New Jersey's Death Penalty", 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Historical Northwestern University Legal Aid, Legal Clinics, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Historical Research on late 19th and early 20th century crimes, 2006; 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Illinois Capital Punishment information - Christopher Tansey Capital Litigation Trust Fund data, Annotation of Capital Punishment Reform Provision, First Degree murder Summary table, State Death Penalty Decision Guidelines, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Lethal Injection - Saddamn Hussein, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Lethal Injection - Henry Weinstein, Los Angeles Times Staff writer, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Glenn L. Pierce and Michael L. Radelet, "The Impact of Legally Inappropriate Factors on Death Sentencing for California Homicides", 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 30)
  - Slides Draft - Illinois Violent Death Reporting System, ca. 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 31)
  - Summary of Indictments for Murder on Illinois in which a notice of intent to seek capital punishment was filed, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 32)
  - Washington State Bar Association: Final Report of the Death Penalty Subcommittee of the committee on Public Defense, 2006 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 33)
  - Cook County Appropriations data, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 34)
  - FBI crime report on Homicides, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 35)
  - Illinois Crime Index Offense/Crime Index Offense Arrest Data, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 36)
  - Illinois Criminal Code - Appellate procedures, reversals, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 37)
  - Illinois Judicial Circuits, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 38)
  - Illinois Law Enforcement training- recording of homicide interrogations, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 39)
  - Illinois Mandate to create Capital Crimes Database, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 40)
  - Illinois Violent Death Reporting System, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 41)
  - Legislative Statutes - New Jersey and New Mexico, 2007; 2009 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 42)
  - Lethal Injection - Animal Liberation Front, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 43)
  - Lethal Injection - AVMA Guidelines on Euthanasia, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 44)
  - Lethal Injection - Deborah W. Denno, "The Lethal Injection Quandary: How Medicine Has Dismantled the Death Penalty, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 45)
  - Lethal Injection - Euthanasia Statutes, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 46)
  - Lethal Injection - Dead Animal disposal, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 47)
  - Lethal Injection - Oregon Death with Dignity Act, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 48)
  - Lethal Injection - Mad Cow, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 49)
  - Lethal Injection - Toledo Blade, Michael Manning botched lethal injection suit, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 50)
  - New Jersey bills repealing the death penalty, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 51)
  - New Jersey Capital Punishment Report - typed notes, ca. 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 52)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Efforts to Improve the Illinois Capital Punishment System: worth the Cost?" (with annotations), 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 53)
  - Table 1 - Results of published studies reporting the costs associated with processing capital cases (from "The Cost of the Death Penalty in Maryland"), ca. 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 54)
  - Wrongful Conviction Awards - Illinois, Washington, California, Nebraska, Utah, 2007 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 55)
  - Leigh B. Bienen, "Not wiser after 35 years of Contemplating the Death Penalty", 2008 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 56)
  - Joseph E. Birkett op-ed on death penalty reforms in 2002, 2008 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 57)
  - Bureau of Justice Statistics Capital Punishment data for 2008 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 58)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund and general costs of death penalty, 2008; 2009 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 59)
  - "Death Penalty Reform in Illinois: Five Years of Failure" - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual Report, 2008 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 60)
  - Jon B. Gould and Lisa Greenman, "Update on the Cost, Quality, and Availability of Defense Representation in Federal Death Penalty Case: Preliminary Report on Phase One of the Research", 2008 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 61)
  - Jon B. Gould and Lisa Greenman, "Update on the Cost, Quality, and Availability of Defense Representation in Federal Death Penalty Case: Preliminary Report on Phase One of the Research", 2008; 2010 (Box 4 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 62)
  - Barbara J. Hayler, "Moratorium and Reform: Illinois's Efforts to Make the Death Penalty Process 'Fair, Just, and Accurate'", 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Jessica S. Henry, "New Jersey's Road to Abolition", 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Court System - expenditures table, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Report, Post - Clemency Era, ca. 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Illinois Crime rate and prison population data, 2008; 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - "Illinois Treasurer proposes reform in litigation Fund", 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Lethal Injection - Jim Speta question about administration of federal Animal Protection Act, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - John Roman et. al., "The Cost of the Death Penalty in Maryland", 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Elliot Slosar, "Costs of Capital Punishment in Illinois", ca. 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Summaries of Illinois Death Row Convictions Since 2003, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Summaries of Illinois Death Row Convictions Since 2003, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Syllabus - Writing for a Professional Audience and Beyond, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Table of Illinois Executions, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Texas capital punishment racial disparities study, 2008; 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - Jeffrey Toobin, "Death in Georgia" (cite in FN), 2008 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - 771 indictments for First Degree Murder in Illinois 2003-2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - A base of Governor Pardoning Power, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Al Baker, "Homicides Near Record Low Rate In New York City" (FN 141), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Katherine Barnes, et. al., "Place Matters (Most): An Empirical Study of Prosecutorial Decision - Making in Death - Eligible Cases" (cited around FN 136), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Appointed Counsel Expenses from Fiscal Years 2000-2009, ca. 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund with notes, 2009; 2010 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - Chicago Murder Conviction Cases, 2004; 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Citation - David Baldus Nebraska Study, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Citation - Nationally death sentences down and reaction to Ohio op-ed arguing that lethal injection is inhumane, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Colorado State Budget, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Cook County Employees Salaries, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Cook County, Illinois Budget - State's Attorney, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Cook County Illinois Obligations, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Cook County Public Defender Salaries, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Philip J. Cook, "Potential Savings from Abolition of the Death Penalty in North Carolina" (with annotations), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2009; 2010 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - Dilliard Cost and Jurisdiction of New Jersey Appellate Courts, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 32)
  - Crime in Illinois 1971 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 33)
  - Crime in Illinois 1985 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 34)
  - Crime in Illinois 2000 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 35)
  - Crime in Illinois 1990 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 36)
  - Crime in Illinois 1998 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 37)
  - Crime in Illinois 2005 - Historical Statistics (used in "Capital Punishment in Illinois in the Aftermath of the Ryan Commutations"), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 38)
  - Brian Dugan Article (FN 194/196), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 39)
  - Brian Dugan defense costs, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 40)
  - Amanda Enyeart - table of Illinois Supreme Court Death Penalty Opinions, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 41)
  - Fiscal Impact of Abolition of death penalty in New Mexico, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 42)
  - Fiscal Impact of Abolition in New Jersey and New Mexico, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 43)
  - Georgia Proportionality Review - Stevens Statement (quote), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 44)
  - Historical Evolution of Illinois Death Penalty Legislation, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 45)
  - Illinois Capital Cases, Cook County, 2009; 2010; Undated (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 46)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 47)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act Amendments, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 48)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Research Material, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 49)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Fund Data - Jonathan Sabo, 2009; 2010 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 50)
  - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual Report, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 51)
  - Illinois crime data from 2003 - 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 52)
  - Illinois Criminal Procedure and Capital Crimes Litigation Acts from 1999 to 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 53)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Reversals Law, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 54)
  - Illinois Health Care Worker Background Check Act, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 55)
  - Illinois House Bill 0262 (Death Penalty Abolition), 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 56)
  - Illinois House Bill 262 - Death Penalty Abolition, 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 57)
  - Illinois Office of the State Appellate Defender - Annual Report Fiscal Year 2009 (Box 5 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 58)
  - Illinois v. Salvador Ortiz - Actual Innocence Case, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Illinois Procedures in Capital Cases (cite), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Illinois Public Defender Compensation - Quote for Public Defender Salaries, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Illinois v. Rolando Cruz (1994), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Illinois State's Attorneys Salaries, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2001, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2002, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 7)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2003, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2004, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2005, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2006, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2007, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2008, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Illinois Wrongful Conviction Settlement Data, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 14)
  - Indiana Public Defender Cuts, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 15)
  - January 1, 2004 report of the Cook County State's Attorney General's Office regarding monies received under Capital Crime Litigation Trust Fund Act, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 16)
  - Journal of Criminal Law & Criminology notes - typed notes from "Capital Punishment in Illinois in the Aftermath of the Ryan Commutations: Reforms, Economic Realities, and a new Saliency for Issues of Cost", 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Jeffrey L. Kirchmeier, et. al., "Vigilante Justice: Prosecutor Misconduct in Capital Cases" (with annotations), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Legislation used in footnotes, Washington House Bill 2864, California Legislation 432, Nebraska Legislation 260, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Marcia Lehr - indigent defense, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 20)
  - New Jersey Amendments to Death Penalty Regulations (cite), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 21)
  - New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall (1992) - cite Handler's dissent, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Supreme Court Justice Daniel O'Hern, "What Makes a Court Supreme", 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 23)
  - "New State Budget Crimps Justice Agencies", 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 24)
  - North Carolina Innocence Inquiry Commission, 2009; 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Northwestern Law Newsletter, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Notes - Illinois death sentences, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Kristen Nugent, "Proportionality and Prosecutorial Discretion" good notes on Co. by Co. and on prosecutorial discretion, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Office of the State Appellate Defender Annual Report, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Research Notes on newspaper accounts of murders in Illinois, ca. 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 30)
  - John Schwartz, "Death Sentence Dropped But Executions Rose in '09" (FN 139), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 31)
  - "Smart on Crime: Reconsidering the Death Penalty in a Time of Economic Crisis" (cite), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 32)
  - Alex Song - Illinois v. Brian Nelson, Illinois v. Hanson, and Illinois v. Banks, 2009; 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 33)
  - State's Attorneys power and dates, discretion, and compensation, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 34)
  - State's Attorney Salaries (quote), 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 35)
  - Texas Governor James Ferguson and payments for pardons, 2009 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 36)
  - 1986 Article on Robert Marshall's First Death Sentence, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 37)
  - 2009 Amendment to Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 38)
  - A Brief History of the Lethal Injection Debate since 2008 Compiled by Mark Christopher Frantz, ca. 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 39)
  - Abolition and State Proposition, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 40)
  - Adams County First Degree Murders request, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 41)
  - Amendment to Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 42)
  - American Law Institute on Capital Punishment, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 43)
  - Attorney General Determination and Federal Death Penalty, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 44)
  - Attorney General and Federal Death Penalty Approval, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 45)
  - Blind Lineups, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 46)
  - Bureau of Justice Statistics Crime and Justice Data Online, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 47)
  - Jon Burge Article (FN 193), 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 48)
  - Capital Crimes Litigation Act - high lighted portions and changes, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 49)
  - Capital Litigation Fund Illinois Report, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 50)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 51)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - 2009 revisions, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 52)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund for Cook County - FOIA Request, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 53)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 54)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, fiscal years 2008 - 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 55)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Printout with notes, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 56)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund Statistical Report, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 57)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund Statistics, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 58)
  - Capital Punishment Reform Study Committee Act of 2003, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 59)
  - Cases that assert no proportionality review for Illinois, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 60)
  - Citation - Illinois Supreme Court Case overturn death penalty, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 61)
  - Connecticut Death Penalty Articles, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 62)
  - Cook County Indictments 2003 - 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 63)
  - Cook County - Capital Litigation Trust Funds, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 64)
  - Correspondence - Eligibility of non - statutory aggravating factors, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 65)
  - Correspondence - wrongful convictions awards (FN), 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 66)
  - John Council, "5th Circuit Judge Notes 'Kafkaesque' Result in Capital Case" (is quoted), 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 67)
  - Crime in Illinois 2003, 2010 (Box 6 (2-Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material), Folder 68)